幽灵战士
不  我需要这个
No, I need this!
不  为了他
No! For him!
不不  他没有足够的食物
No! No! There isn't enough food for him!
我受够了你们这些怪物
I'm so sick of you monsters!
不
No!
这边  来啊
Over here! Come on!
来啊  来抓我
Come on. Come and get me.
来啊
Come on.
这边
Hey. Over here.
好  这次算我求你了
Okay, this time, I'm begging.
来啊  来啊
Come on. Come on.
是你  真正的幽灵战士
It's you -- the real one.
幽灵战士
希望你这次没带忘啤酒
I hope you didn't forget the beer this time.
我在小巷里撞见了自己  就把时间忘了
I lost track of time when I ran into myself in the alley.
你自己
Yourself?
显然  我不再是唯一一个
Apparently, I am no longer the only ghost
在我们城市的街道上巡逻的幽灵战士
patrolling the streets of our fair city.
是吗  有人剽窃了你的行为啊
Yeah? Somebody stole your act, huh?
我只希望他们装作是我
I just hope they don't get themselves killed
别把自己害死就行
pretending they're me.
你还好吗
How are you?
我们继续聊天  行吗
Let's just keep talking, okay?
你得到了什么情报  有没有有价值的
What kind of intel did you get? Anything worth a damn?
我画出了这个营地的四分之三
I got three-quarters of this camp mapped.
但我搞不明白警报拉响时
But I can't figure out where these Skitters are coming from
教堂附近的迅猎兽是从哪里来的
when the alarm goes off near that church.
没有警戒塔  没有检查站
There's no guard tower, there's no checkpoint,
我没法调查那些街道
and I can't see into those streets.
我们需要鸟瞰图
We need a bird's-eye view.
不  你在做什么
No! What are you doing?!
不  你不能带我走
No! You're not taking me!
搞什么
What the hell?
你们这些该死的蟑螂
You damn roaches!
这事结束后  你们会血溅街头
You'll be bleeding in the streets when this is over!
它们是不是让我们离开了禁闭室
Did they just lock us out of solitary?
看来它们把我们扔在同一个火坑
Looks like they're throwing us all in the same frying pan.
爸爸
Dad!
哈尔
Hal?
Hal.
你没事吧
You all right?
上校
Colonel.
它们打不垮你老爹  你知道的
They can't break your old man. You know that.
-泰克多  -你好  教授
- Tec. - Hey, professor.
哈尔
Hal.
为什么放你们出来
Why did they let you guys out?
我不知道  情况有变
I don't know. Something's changed.
有黑色的大飞虫
We've got these big, black
进入营地
flying things been coming into camp.
看起来像是大黄蜂
The ones that look like hornets.
是啊  它们把小孩带出了营地
Yeah. They've been taking all the kids out of the camp.
它们带走了珍  恐怕也带走了马特
They got Jeanne. I'm afraid they might have gotten Matt.
别担心  我们会找回他们的
Don't worry. We're gonna get them all back.
我们会找到珍
We're gonna find Jeanne.
找到马特  本  亚蕾克西和安
We're gonna find Matt and then Ben and Lexi and Anne.
然后我们就永远端掉艾士芬尼...
And then we're gonna take the Espheni out permanen--
那是什么
What's that?
大家后退
Everybody, back!
大家都后退
Everybody, get back!
你们的游戏结束了
Your games have come to an end.
他有脊甲
He's harnessed.
看来上面有人想给我们传递一个信号
Looks like somebody up there is trying to send us a signal.
除非你们交出被称为幽灵战士的恐怖分子
There will be no more food drops
否则不会再投递食物了
until you surrender the terrorist you call the Ghost.
我们已经清空了禁闭室
We've emptied your solitary ward,
允许你们最残忍的罪犯通过抓捕他
allowing your most ruthless criminals to save themselves
来拯救自己
by hunting him down.
找出这个义务警员的人会得到奖励
Whoever identifies this vigilante will be rewarded.
任何帮助他的人都将被处决
Anyone found aiding him will be executed.
这不是警告
This is not a warning.
交出幽灵战士
Hand over the Ghost.
幽灵战士
归根到底  他不是你们的朋友
He is not, as it turns out, your friend after all.
选择权在你们手上
The choice is yours.
《陨落星辰》
第四季第二集
汤姆  别告诉我你要去做蠢事
You tell me, Tom, that you're not gonna do anything stupid!
什么叫"蠢"
Define "stupid."
这些人已经在挨饿了
Look, these people are starving already.
没有了配给食物  他们几天内就会死
Without rations, they're gonna be dead in a matter of days.
-还有别的方法  -好样的  比如呢
- There are other ways to deal with this. - Great. Like how?
比如珀普
Like Pope.
我们会跟踪他  找到他的藏货
We'll track him down. We'll find his stash.
你觉得他藏的食物够几百人吃吗
You think he's got enough food to feed a couple hundred people?
我了解珀普  他藏的食物够全州人吃
Knowing Pope, he's got enough to feed the whole damn state!
这不是长久之计
It's not a permanent solution.
至少是缓兵之计  对吧
Yeah, but it's something, isn't it?
确实会给我们争取一点时间
It'll buy us a little time.
很好
Good. All right.
听着  你不许去自首
And listen, you're not turning yourself in.
这没的商量  知道吗
That's off the table. Got it?
哈尔  你有没有更多情报
Hal, were you able to get any more intel
说明迅猎兽是从教堂后面哪个地方出现的
on where the Skitters are coming from behind the church?
还没有
No, not yet.
不知怎么  它们在十七秒内
Somehow, they're making it around that corner
就能绕过拐角处  到达城市广场
and into the town square in under 17 seconds.
如果我要吸引它们的火力
If I'm gonna draw their fire --
你最好知道它们是从哪个地方来的
You better know where they're coming from.
逃生路线怎么样了
What about the escape route?
我们让挖隧道的人又往下了十英尺
Uh, we had our tunnelers go down another 10 feet.
电网还在
The wall is still there.
那我们没法从电网下过去了吗
So we're not going under it?
没错  但我们在电网南边找到了一些碎石
Right. But we found some rubble against the south wall.
也许能爬过去
We might be able to climb over it.
你能破坏电网吗
Were you able to disrupt the power to the fence?
我们用那个小发电机试了试
We threw that little generator at it.
连闪都没闪一下
It barely even flickered.
那我们要怎么办
So, how are we gonna do it?
不怎么办
Well, we're not.
计划要顺利进行  这电网就得倒
Well, for the plan to work, the wall has to come down.
-怎么了  -计划有变
- What? - The plan's changed.
你都没知会我一声就改变了计划
You changed the plan without talking to me?
我现在正跟你说呢
Well, I'm talking to you right now.
不  不能这样
No. This can't happen.
必须这样
Well, it's got to happen.
我知道你认为
Now, look, I know you think
这一切由你负责
you got this whole thing on your shoulders,
但你被关起来了
but you've been locked up.
你让我做主了
You left me in charge.
现在我需要你相信我
Now I need you to trust me
我认为有更好的方法
when I say I think I know there's a better way.
因为我认识个人  能帮我们出去
'Cause I know someone who can get us out of here.
他需要水
He needs water!
把他的背包拿下来
Take off his backpack.
拿着他的装备  你们分担一下
Grab his gear. Split it between you.
继续喝
Keep drinking.
接着走
Let's keep moving!
安
Anne.
我们不能停下  安东尼
We're not stopping, Anthony.
我们可以整日或整夜前行  但不能日夜兼行
Look, we can march all day or all night, but we can't do both.
艾士芬尼正用这些路
The Espheni are using these roads
将孩子们拖去不知什么鬼地方
to haul children to God knows where,
也就是说我女儿很有可能
which means there's a damn good chance
就在路的尽头
my daughter's at the end of the line.
所以我们才跟着你走
Look, that's why we're following you!
大家都有想找到的家人
Everyone has family they're trying to find.
我只是不想
I'm just trying to keep
沿途再有伤亡
from losing anyone else along the way.
如果她一直这么冲动用事
How long does she expect to keep going
还能走多远
if she keeps giving her rations away?
我们都脱水了  困了...
The rest of us are dehydrated, aslee--
它从灌木丛里出来的  没看到同党
It came through the brush. I don't see any others.
还活着
It's still alive.
让我来
Allow me.
不行  它是我的
No. He's mine.
她在干什么
What's she doing?
学习  冥想  逃离他们
Learning, meditating, escaping from them.
他们想从她身上得到什么
What do they want from her?
一切
Everything.
他们好像认为她是神
I think they think she's God.
很高兴你来了
I'm glad you're here.
需要有人来告诉亚蕾克西真相
Lexi needs someone who will tell her the truth.
什么真相
What truth?
她快死了
She's dying.
什么
What?
不不  她  她看着...
No. No. She's -- she looks --
她看着像21岁  实际上还不到一岁
She looks like she's 21. She's barely a year old.
我搞不懂她急速发育的原因
I can't figure out her growth spurts.
好像完全没规律
They seem totally random.
我也不知道她以这样莫测的成长速度
And I don't know how long she can last
继续下去还能坚持多久
when she's aging at this unpredictable rate.
她的DNA突变  部分人类  部分外星人
Her DNA's a mutation -- part human, part alien.
但这种组合又...
But something about the combination has...
产生了一种我从未见过的有机体
resulted in an organism unlike anything I've ever seen.
那你准备怎么办
So... what are you gonna do?
不知道
I don't know.
也许做什么都是错
It might be a mistake to do anything.
自然的奇迹就源于不可能的组合
Nature's miracles spring from unlikely combinations.
有时  一加一等于三
Sometimes, one plus one equals three.
-你得帮帮她  -我也想
- You have to help her. - I want to.
我们刚到这里的那几个月
The first few months we were here,
是我照顾亚蕾克西
I took care of Lexi.
我监控着她的人类荷尔蒙水平
I monitored her human hormonal levels,
血糖和细胞复制速度
blood sugar, rate of cell replication.
我保持她的稳定
I kept her stable
并努力搞清楚她生长的变动性
while trying to understand the volatility of her aging,
她也信任我
and she trusted me.
但是...
But...
当她阻止了那个械甲怪  然后
When she stopped that Mech and all this --
这些人都簇拥着她
all of this sprung up around her,
我再也无法靠近她了
I couldn't get near her anymore.
谁挡着你
Who was stopping you?
卢尔德严格下令不让我接近她
Lourdes put out strict orders to keep me away.
她说我让亚蕾克西不高兴
She says I upset Lexi...
还说我是无信仰者
that I'm a nonbeliever.
但你不是  对吗
But you're not, are you?
梅森先生  什么是新联盟
Mr. Mason, what is the New Coalition?
我们就是  领队
We are, team leader.
在艾士芬尼指引下光明的下一代
The next generation to walk the Espheni path.
我们将拯救地球及人类
We will save the Earth and its people.
要怎么做
How will you do that?
首先  我们要拯救自己的家人
First, we save our families.
怎么拯救
And how will you do that?
找到他们  拉响警报
I'll find them and raise the alarm.
我们为什么要怎么做
And why will we do this?
因为我爱他们
Because I love them.
说得好  梅森先生  请座吧
Nice work, Mr. Mason. You may take your seat.
希拉
Sheila.
我想请你上前来
I'd now like to invite you up front.
说得好  梅森先生  我都差点让你骗了
Nice work, Mr. Mason. You almost fooled me.
今天是个特殊的日子
Today is a very special day.
希拉要毕业了
Sheila is graduating.
午餐后  老时间
希拉的父母就是所谓的"叛乱分子"
Sheila's parents are what some call "insurgents"
或者说"恐怖分子"
or "terrorists."
地球上的一些成人
Some adults on Earth
对政府和领导人过于愤世嫉俗
have become so cynical about governments and leaders
无法信任我们的艾士芬尼兄弟们
that they have a hard time trusting our Espheni brothers.
希拉的父母就是反叛者的成员
Sheila's parents are part of this web of rebellion
这会引发无谓的攻击
That is launching unprovoked attacks.
幸好  我们截获了希拉母亲发的一条消息
Luckily, we intercepted a message from Sheila's mother
问道  是否有人见过她的女儿
Asking if anyone had seen her daughter.
她非常爱你
She really loves you.
我也爱她
I love her, too.
那么  你准备怎么做
So, what are you going to do?
我要找到她  拉响警报
I'll find her and raise the alarm.
但是要在...
But not before...
她带我回到藏身之处之后
She takes me back to their hiding place
这样我们就可以拯救所有叛乱者了
So we can save all the insurgents.
完全正确
Exactly.
愿意领我们背诵宣言吗
Will you lead us in the pledge?
地球是天赐之福
The Earth is a gift.
新联盟必须和艾士芬尼兄弟们一同保护地球
The New Coalition must protect it with our Espheni brothers.
我们同心协力  必将共创美好新世界
Joined together, we will build a beautiful world.
你是疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
为什么跟着我
Why are you following me?
我在找你的存货
I'm here for your stash.
没错
That's right.
我看见你溜到迅猎兽背后
I saw you slide behind the Skitters,
吃它们吃剩的
lapping up their crumbs,
或从无力反抗的人那里偷食物
stealing food from decent people who can't defend themselves.
我尽力获取所需  和别人没有分别
I took what I could, no different than anybody else.
何况你和梅森掌管这里这么久
Besides, you and Mason have been in charge all this time.
看我们成了什么样子
Look where we are.
谁是"我们"  珀普
Who's this "we," Pope?
据我所知  你可是个非常称职的
As far as I can tell, you're doing a perfectly fine job
无道德懦夫叛徒
of behaving like a craven, immoral turncoat
心里只有自己
all by yourself.
把藏货交出来
Hand over your stash.
自己来拿
Come and get it.
珀普  韦弗  我们知道你在下面
Pope, weaver! yeah. We know you're down here.
有人跟踪你  你...
Somebody followed you, you...
看来  你们俩是一伙的
So, you two are working together.
-不是  -不是
- No!  - No!
我知道你一直在偷东西
Look, I know you've been stealing.
只是不知道你藏在哪儿了
I just didn't know where you kept it...
现在知道了
Till now.
我谢谢你全家
Thanks for that, by the way.
听我说  小伙子们
Listen, boys,
我和你们来这的目的一样
I'm here for the same reason you are --
要找到这里藏着的食物
to find whatever food is hidden down here
然后分发给大家
and distribute it to everybody.
分个屁  我们饿了
Screw that. We're hungry.
我们要吃东西...  马上
We're gonna eat... now.
你少给我动手
Don't you do it.
别浪费时间了  珀普  快
Don't waste your time, Pope. Come on.
快走
Come on!
-丁甘  -汤姆·梅森
- Dingaan.  - Tom Mason.
见到你很高兴
My pleasure.
谢谢你能见我
Thanks for meeting me.
那是短波电台吗
Is that a shortwave?
对  而且还能用
Yeah, man. And it works.
如果外面还有人在听的话
That is, if there's someone out there to hear it.
你可以试试看
You're welcome to try.
恭敬不如从命
I might take you up on that.
哈尔说你是南非来的
Hal tells me you're from South Africa.
对
Uh...yeah.
约翰内斯堡
Johannesburg.
我失去了妻儿
I lost my wife and son.
首次入侵还是壁垒落下的时候
In the initial invasion or when the walls came down?
首次入侵
Invasion.
很遗憾
I'm sorry.
我也是
As am I.
之后一直潜逃
Been running ever since,
从三所艾士芬尼监狱逃脱
escaping Espheni prisons -- three of them.
里士满  格林斯博罗  夏洛特市
Richmond, Greensboro, Charlotte.
佩服
Impressive.
黑蜂兽在我往南卡罗来纳州穿越的时候
Hornets found me crossing into South Carolina,
把我抓到这里来了
Brought me here.
跟我说说越狱的事
Tell me about the escapes.
每座监狱各不相同
Every camp is different,
只有一个共同之处  绿色壁垒
but one thing is a constant -- the Green Barrier.
要越过它  你需要这个
To go over it, you need one of these.
法拉第屏蔽服
A faraday suit.
在翻越电网的时候  让电流从周遭流过
It allows electricity to flow around me as I climb the fence.
你是物理学家
You're a physicist?
电气工人
Electrical lineman.
我可以教你怎么制造  只要给我找到铜
I will teach you how to build one if you help me find copper.
没有铜  屏蔽服无法使用
Without it, the suit won't work.
我知道有人藏了废金属
I know some guys that are hoarding some scrap metal.
可以找他们谈谈
I can talk to them.
屏蔽服是很不错  但只能一个人穿
The suit's great, but it's only for one person.
我要让所有人都出来
We need to get everybody out.
不  我们要想办法把电网电源关掉
No, we need to figure out a way to cut the power to the fence.
黑蜂兽带我飞入这个营地时
When the Hornets flew me into this camp,
我看到了一个传感器连接一条链条
I saw a sensor and a tether coming off it.
但是看不到通向哪里
I couldn't see where it led.
-你觉得那是电源线吗  -有可能
- Do you think that tether's a power cord?  - Could be.
如果真是这样  我还真能用上你的屏蔽服
Well, if that's true, then maybe I could use one of your suits.
我可以翻过电网  剪断链条
I could climb the wall, cut the tether,
切断电网的电源线
And it will bring the power to the walls down.
爸爸  你不是一个人  知道吗
Dad, it's not all on you, remember?
有道理
Fair enough.
我们还需要想办法
We still need to figure out
能让几百人都出来
how to get hundreds of people out of here.
我可以分散迅猎兽的注意
I could cause a distraction, have all the Skitter guards
大家越狱的时候  让它们跟着我走
follow me while everybody else escapes.
但我们还需要一个人
But then we'd still need someone
穿上屏蔽服翻过电网
to get in the suit and climb the wall.
简单
Easy.
所以我们又回到先前的问题了
That brings us back to the missing piece of the puzzle --
教堂周围的迅猎兽到底在哪里
where the Skitters are clustered near that church.
看来答案都在那里了
Looks like all the answers are right there.
我一个人也能对付他们
I could have taken those guys.
没什么比看你被揍
Oh, there's nothing I would have liked better
更能让我高兴的了
than to see you get your ass kicked.
可是他们有刀  而且还以为我们是同伙
They had knives, and they thought that we were partners.
我可不想因为你死掉
I'm not getting killed for you.
-希望他们喜欢豆子  -什么
- Well, I hope they like beans. - What?
我的存货就是八罐豆子
My stash consisted of eight cans of beans.
你怎么不早说
Why didn't you say that?
总有一天我要东山再起
Hey, man, one day, I'm gonna be back in business.
在那之前  我得保证我的名号不倒啊
Till then, I got a reputation to uphold.
我当时都打算揍你了
I was ready to kick your ass back there,
不过我也很愿意现在动手
but I'm happy to do it here.
这是你今天说的最智慧的一句话
Well, now, that's the smartest thing you have said all day.
等等
Hold on.
怎么啦  你还得先睡会儿
What? You need to take a nap, huh?
还是需要个热身运动  能量饮料什么的
You need to stretch out, a little shot of gatorade?
-怎么啦  -你能闭嘴吗
- What? - Would you shut up?!
什么声音
What is that sound?
科奇斯  我是汤姆·梅森  能听到吗
Cochise, this is Tom Mason. Do you read?
科奇斯  我是汤姆·梅森  能收到吗
Cochise? This is tom mason. Are you out there?
汤姆·梅森  收到
Tom Mason, I read you.
能用
It's working!
要是我父亲发现他给我的通讯器
My father would be surprised to find the communicator he left me
被改装成了更低端的设备肯定要惊讶了
has been retrofitted to a lesser technology.
你得与时俱进嘛  朋友
You got to -- you got to change with the times, my friend,
就算是倒退也没办法
even if it's backwards.
我知道这件事很危险
I know it's a bit of a crapshoot,
但是我们需要食物和补给
but we're hurting for food and supplies.
我的队伍和你们的集中营之间
There are substantial Espheni forces
有大量的艾士芬尼势力
between my team and your camp.
还有什么新消息吗
What else is new?
说实话  很多
A great deal, as a matter of fact.
我们确认了
We have confirmed that the Espheni
艾士芬尼在建造新的能源站
are constructing a new power station.
是用来给以前的电力网供能的吗
Is this, uh, designed to power a grid like the one before?
电力网和在我来之前你摧毁的那种
No. That grid, along with the Espheni jamming device
艾士芬尼屏蔽仪都是防御措施
you destroyed before my arrival, were defensive measures.
新的能源是艾士芬尼用以攻击的
The new power source would allow the Espheni to go on offense.
用以攻击
On offense?
这可不像什么好事
That... doesn't sound very good.
这个问题到时候再说吧
Uh, w-w-well, let's burn that bridge when we come to it.
但现在最大的问题是没有食物
Right now I've got some very hungry people.
抱歉
I am sorry.
现在我没法给你弄到食物
I cannot get food to you at this time.
不过如果你能逃出来
However, if you do manage to escape,
我倒是知道你能在哪找到食物
I can tell you where there is food.
那就将来再说吧
Well, we got that to look forward to, then.
我还有个好消息告诉你
I do have one piece of encouraging news.
我们的一架无人机发现
One of our recon drones observed children
有孩子被送去了南边一个集中营
being transported to a camp south of here.
我们认为马特也在那里
We believe Matt has been taken there.
你能把他救出来吗  科奇斯
Can you get him? Cochise?
我得先和我队伍的人商量
I must confer with my team.
你想和谁商量都行  但是
No, no, w-w-- yes, confer with whoever you want, but...
但是这是我现在
but that's about the -- the worst thing
最无法拖延的事了
that you could dangle in front of me right now.
我是他父亲  却没法保护他
I'm his father, and I can't protect him.
你能救救他吗  求你了  科奇斯
Can you get to him, please? Please, Cochise.
我会在一个小时内出发
I will leave within the hour.
结束
Signing off.
丹妮会为我们翻译
Denny's gonna translate for us.
你好好回答我的问题  我就不杀你
You tell me what I want to know, and I won't kill you.
懂了吗
Understand?
懂了
I understand.
我们拦截了一辆运送孩子的车
We stopped a transport truck filled with children.
他们本来要去哪里
Where were they being taken?
要去重新接受教育以便迎接新秩序的来临
Re-education to help them be successful in the new order.
什么新秩序
What new order?
艾士芬尼和人类联手  由混血带领
Espheni and human together, led by the Hybrid.
混血
The Hybrid?
混血才是我们的未来
The Hybrid is our future.
亚蕾克西  是她吗  是不是
Lexi. Is this her? Is this --
你说的是她吗  我女儿
is this who you're talking about? My daughter?
她就是你说的未来吗  是吗
Is she the future? Is she the future you're talking about?
我不知道  我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
告诉我  你们把她带到哪儿去了
Tell me! Where is she being taken?!
-不要  -她在哪儿
- Oh, no. - Where is she?!
-不要  -你们把她带到哪去了
- Oh, no. - Where is she being taken?!
不要
Oh, no.
别插队  梅森
Hey. Can't cut in line, Mason.
这些人会把你脑袋弄下来
These people will cut your head off.
我要去见我妹妹还要排队吗
I'm not waiting in line to see my sister.
好孩子
Attaboy.
借过
Excuse me.
她要赐予我们的  她有
... us all of her offerings. She's got --
你不能进去
you can't go in there.
我可以
Yes, I can.
我们要想拦住你是轻而易举的
If we want to stop you, we can.
你为什么要拦住我
Why would you want to stop me?
就因为我是她哥哥所以她也许会听我的吗
Because I'm her older brother and she might listen to me?
因为你和无信仰者站在一起了
'Cause you've aligned yourself with a nonbeliever.
你是说卡达尔博士吗
You mean Dr. Kadar?
你知道他有名字的
You know his name.
为什么要这样做  你是个医生
Why are you acting like this? You're a doctor.
当医生也没法保证我安全
Being a doctor didn't keep me safe, okay?
亚蕾克西可以
Lexi did.
她取走了我的眼线虫  使我不被控制
She removed the scales from my eyes, and I was healed.
她救了我  所以我要保护她
She saved me. And I will protect her.
本
Ben?
亚蕾克西
Lexi.
我想跟你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
当然可以  进来吧
Of course. Come in.
单独谈  本
Only you, Ben.
这里难道不美吗
Isn't it beautiful in here?
比外面好多了
So much nicer than it is out there.
没有喧嚣  也无吵闹
All the noise, the crowds.
械甲怪的事情
The Mechs.
你听说了
You heard about that.
大家对此津津乐道
That's a story these people will never stop telling.
他们认为是你毁了它
They think you destroyed it.
是真的吗
Did you?
我感受到空气中的电力开始聚集
I could feel the electricity gathering in the atmosphere.
感觉到了械甲怪启动时
I could feel the frequency necessary
所需要的电力频率
for the Mech to operate.
我很害怕
I was afraid.
然后械甲怪就停下来了
And the Mech came down.
我很担心你
I'm worried about you.
为什么
Why?
卡达尔博士认为你有危险
Dr. Kadar thinks you're in danger.
他想帮你检查一下
He wants to examine you.
卢尔德不同意
Lourdes says no.
卢尔德想要通过控制你来得到权力
Lourdes is trying to gain power by controlling you.
我并不听命于她
I answer to a higher power.
亚蕾克西  我觉得你有危险
Lexi... I think you're in danger,
而且我不相信这里的人能保护你
and I'm not convinced that the people here have your back.
这个营地甚至没有守卫
There's not even anyone guarding the camp.
只要我们和平  世界就和平
As long as we are peaceful, the world is peaceful.
你说话能别跟庙里的签一个调调吗
Will you please stop talking like a damn fortune cookie.
你想让我怎么说话
How would you like me to talk?
教育我如何与他人交流吗
Do you have a manual for how I should communicate?
你觉得你比狄更斯更有水平吗
You think you're a better teacher than Dickens
或是莎士比亚  或是你的上帝
or Shakespeare or your own God?!
是吗
Do you?!
Do you?
亚蕾克西
Lexi...
战争就要开始了...
There is a war on, and...
而我们的家人  依旧不知所踪
our family -- we have no idea where they are.
爸爸  马特  哈尔  你妈妈
Dad, Matt, Hal, your mother.
他们都会来的  本
They're all coming, Ben.
他们很快就会来  在那之前  我们很安全
They'll all be here soon. Until then, we're safe.
你不记得壁垒落下时的样子了吗
You don't remember what it was like when the Barriers fell.
我记得很清楚
I remember everything.
我记得你抱着我
I remember you holding me to your chest,
还说"我会保护你"
saying, "I will protect you."
我会的  我是你哥哥
I will. I'm -- I'm your brother.
别人想伤害你  得先踏过我的尸体
I'll die before I let anyone hurt you.
如果你希望我去找卡达尔博士  我会的
If you want me to see Dr. Kadar, I will.
你确定吗
You sure about this?
你不觉得我们应该等等韦弗上校吗
Don't you think we ought to wait for Colonel Weaver?
我们总得想办法收集信息
We need to get the information one way or the other.
你怎么知道它们不会直接杀了你
How do you know they're not just gonna take you up there and kill you?
如果他它们想杀我  我早死了
If they wanted me dead, I'd be dead.
-爸爸  -它们有很多杀我的机会  哈尔
- Dad -- - They've had plenty of chances, Hal.
你知道该怎么办
You know what to do.
如果出什么事  你要取代我的位置
And if anything goes wrong, I need you to take over for me.
这些人信任你
These people trust you.
我也相信你
I do, too.
我爱你
I love you.
他来了
There he is.
是汤姆
It's Tom!
汤姆·梅森
Tom Mason?!
你想找我吗  我来了
You want me?! Here I am!
不要
No!
汤姆
Tom!
欢迎啊  汤姆·梅森
Welcome, Tom Mason.
你知道我的名字
You know my name.
没错
I do.
你知道他的名字吗
Do you know his name --
这位被你用来传话的倒霉孩子
this poor kid you're using as a mouthpiece?
他不重要
He's not important.
我不同意
I disagree.
你敢现身出来吗
Are you gonna show yourself,
还是说你太害怕  不敢自己动手
or are you too afraid to come out and do your own dirty work?
没什么要动手的
There's nothing dirty to be done.
我只是有个提议
I have a simple proposition.
你是个领袖
You're a leader.
我们打仗时需要你
We need you to be part of our war effort.
不可能
That's not gonna happen.
如果你帮我们打败一个强大的共同敌人
You will help us thwart a greater common enemy
那么  你就救下了你的家人
and, in so doing, spare your own family.
你最好别提我的家人
I wouldn't mention my family.
我很了解你  汤姆·梅森
I know more about you than just your name, Tom Mason.
我们没有共同敌人
We don't have a common enemy.
沃尔姆是我们的盟友
The Volm are our allies.
比起即将到来的危险  沃尔姆根本不值一提
The Volm are no match for the danger that's coming.
什么危险
What danger would that be?
你无法想象的强大力量
A force far greater than your mind can comprehend.
但是我们
But defeating them
离开了自己的星球
is why we strayed so far from our own galaxy,
一路上收集了这么多资源
why we collected resources
就是为了打败他们
from every planet and moon along the way.
大战很快就要开始了  为了面对战争
The great battle is coming, and in order to face it,
我们必须组建一支崭新的前线部队
we are creating a new, elite, frontline army.
是吗  你说的就是
Oh, is that where the, uh,
那些又黑又大的飞虫吗
big, black, flying things come from?
那些是我们守卫之中的叛徒
Those are traitors from the ranks of our guards.
迅猎兽叛党吗
Rebel Skitters?
通过基因改造  变成无意识的无人机
Genetically altered into mindless drones...
完全听命于我们
completely under our control.
自由意志可能会变得很危险
Free will can be dangerous,
这点不用我说你也知道
but I don't have to tell you that.
其它的守卫虽表现出色  但能力有限
The other guards performed admirably, but they are limited.
将人类的孩子脊甲化才是长期之策
Harnessing human children proved to be unpredictable long-term.
我们正为战争培养更聪颖
We are perfecting a smarter, more plentiful soldier
以及更大量的士兵
for the fight.
挑选出一部分素质优良的成人
Selected human adults.
你们的身躯已完成生长
Your bodies have finished growing.
性格与素质已充分定型
Your personalities and predispositions are set.
你们不是早就在凯伦身上试验过这套吗
Didn't you already try that with Karen?
结果可不甚如意
That didn't work out too well for you.
我们疏忽了  没有除去凯伦的自由意志
We neglected to strip Karen of free will.
我们已改正了错误
We corrected that mistake.
我们将在48小时候后准时开始
We will begin transforming our selected human adults
转化被选中的成人
in precisely 48 hours.
如果我们拒绝服从呢
What happens when we refuse to go along?
目前为止我们所做的一切
Did you willingly go along
你们何曾顺意服从过
with anything we've chosen to do so far?
我们会挑选你们种族中
We will select the best
最聪颖最优秀的人加入我们
and the brightest of your race to join us.
我们花费数月时间才完善好转化过程
This is a process we've taken months to perfect.
在我们谈话之际  准备已然在进行当中
We're doing it even now, as we speak.
任何作出抵抗的人类
Anyone who resists will simply serve
将会成为失去意识的空壳
in a less-conscious form.
这是什么意思
What does that mean?
你很快就会知道了
You'll find out soon enough,
如果你拒绝我们的提议的话
because your family will be first in line
你的家人将会是首批的实验对象
if you refuse our offer.
珀普
Pope!
看
Look.
等等  这是电网的一部分
Wait a second. That's part of the wall.
意味着在电网的另一头
Which means that whatever is on the other side of it
就是墙外的世界
is outside the wall.
外面有日光
That's daylight.
你正是我们所需要的领袖人物
You're the kind of leader we need.
若你肯协助转化计划的完成
Help this transition go smoothly,
你的家人将被赦免
and your family will be spared.
我要马上听到你的答案
I need your answer now.
走起
Let's roll!
你要做出决定
You have a decision to make.
你和你的家人能免于加入
You and your family can be spared
即将发生的伟大的转换计划
from the great transformation that is to come.
你的领袖能力以及勇气
Your leadership and courage
将会成为我们的战斗机器及新军队之间
will be invaluable as the crucial human link
最强而有力的人类连接
between our war machine and the new army.
做出选择吧  汤姆·梅森  进化或是灭亡
Choose, Tom Mason -- evolution or extinction?
吃我们一记  混蛋们
Here! Come get some, you bastards!
炸你个粉身碎骨
Tick, tick, boom, baby!
为什么会有那么多个幽灵战士
How can there be more than one ghost?
你的朋友们会付出惨痛的代价
Your friends will pay severely.
原来它们聚集在这里...
That's where they're clustering...
地底巢穴
underground hatch.
它们所有的能量
All its power...
都来源于此
is from here.
通过系链传递而下
Down the tether.
我此行的目的达到了
Got what I came for.
-马特  -我一直在等你
- Matt. - I was waiting for you.
想着我们可以一起过去
I thought we could walk over together.
好的
Okay.
但我们可以牵手吗
But should we be doing this?
新联盟
The New Coalition
没有禁止牵手的规则
doesn't have any rules against holding hands...
至少我不知道有这样的规则
At least, I don't think they do.
我们可以问问肯特
We could ask Kent.
快走吧  我们要迟到了
Come on. We're going to be late.
好极了
A-awesome.
他们在哪儿
Where are they?
我也不知道
I don't know.
我们是晚了点儿  但他们应该会等我们
We're a little late, but they should have waited for us.
午饭后  老时间
快离开这  米拉
Get out of here, Mira.
-怎么了  -先离开就是了
- What? - Just go.
快走
Hurry. Go.
有什么能帮到你吗  梅森先生
Can I help you, Mr. Mason?
只是想来找斯科普
I was just looking for Skip.
-斯科普毕业了  -什么时候
- Skip graduated. - When?
他从没跟我说过
He didn't say anything.
有些人很注重隐私
Some people like their privacy.
另一个男孩明天会搬进来  海克特
Another boy will be moving in tomorrow -- Hector.
他很聪明  你会喜欢他的
He's very bright. You're gonna like him.
你知道吗  马特
You know, Matt,
我认为你有很大的潜力
I see all sorts of potential in you,
所以我会特别留意你
so I'm gonna keep my eye on you.
谢谢领队
Thank you, team leader.
还好吗亚蕾克西  要什么东西吗
You okay, Lexi? You need anything?
我没事  本  谢了
Yeah, I'm fine, Ben. Thanks.
这是什么
What is that?
一加一等于三  超常现象
One plus one equals three.
-亚蕾克西  -抱歉本  没拦住她
- Ohh, Lexi. - I'm sorry, Ben.
你要对她做什么
What are you doing to her?
这跟你没任何关系  卢尔德
This has nothing to do with you, Lourdes.
把血给我  我是她的医生
Give me that. I'm her doctor.
她授意我这样做
She consented to this procedure.
-别这样卢尔德  -她没权利
- Let it go, Lourdes. - She can't consent.
只有我能给授意你  而我不想你碰她
Only I can consent, and I don't want you touching her.
你是不想让真相大白
You don't want the truth to come out,
但真相能救她的命
but the truth could save her.
你这样会杀了她
You're trying to kill her.
你想捏造事实  说她有病
You want to put a name to it, say she's sick.
她没病
She's not sick.
-放手  -不  不行
- Let go! - No, no!
卢尔德  你得离我妹妹远点
Lourdes, you have to stay away from my sister!
你不配拥有她
You're not worthy of her,
不配拥有我们建造的这一切
of what we've built here.
别吵了
Stop fighting!
你想要战争  想要杀更多的人
You want war, more killing.
你在打破和平
You're breaking the peace!
我不会让你杀了她
I won't let you kill her.
卢尔德  离我妹妹远点
Lourdes, get away from my sister!
卢尔德  卢尔德
Lourdes! Lourdes!
停下  停下
Stop! Stop!
她怎么样了
How is she?
平静多了
She's calmer.
睡着了
She's sleeping.
希望她能睡着
I hope she's sleeping.
这里到底怎么了  玛吉
What the hell's going on here, Maggie?
是她干的吗
Did she do that?
这里发生了很多奇怪的事
I lot of weird things have been happening around here.
我都不知道该怎么想了
I don't know what to think anymore.
卢尔德  她是在利用亚蕾克西
Lourdes...  she's using Lexi.
是的  她完全被蒙蔽了
Yeah, she's got her totally snowed.
亚蕾克西只是个小孩子  她很天真
Lexi's just a little kid. She's naive.
别人会控制她  利用她的能力
Someone could manipulate her into using her abilities
去做一些坏事
for something bad.
那我们该怎么办
So what do we do?
从早到晚看着她
Keep an eye on her day and night.
不要让我们不信任的人接近她
Don't let anyone have access to her we don't trust,
-包括卢尔德  -这可不容易做到
- including Lourdes. - That's not gonna be easy.
我不管  我们必须要这么做
I don't care. We have to do it.
如果有人想见她  必须经过我同意
If someone wants to get to her, they have to go through me.
怎么了
What?
真高兴这里终于来了一个神志清醒的人
It's nice to have another sane person in this place.
你是指跟你想法一样的人
You mean someone you agree with?
先不要操之过急  好吗
Let's not get ahead of ourselves. Okay.
我是指能说的上话的人
I mean someone I can talk to.
我根本没法跟这里的人交谈
There's no one to talk to around here.
他们都走火入魔了
Everyone's drunk the Kool-Aid.
我真高兴你来这了
I'm glad you're here.
我可不愿意来这
I'm not.
但既然无法改变  我也很高兴有你在
But if I have to be, I'm glad I have you.
我想我还是再去看看她吧
I think I'll go check in on her one more time.
好的  明天早晨见
All right, I'll see you in the morning. Yeah.
我不应该在迅猎兽
I shouldn't have killed the Skitter
还联系着你的时候杀死它
while you were connected to it.
我当时没考虑到你
I didn't think.
我知道  我能感觉到你当时失控了
I know. I could feel you losing control.
它也能感觉到
So could it.
你能看到它的想法
You could read its thoughts.
你知道亚蕾克西在哪儿吗
Did you see where Lexi is?
它不知道
It didn't know.
但当它说起混血时
But something very weird happened
发生了件很奇怪的事
when...it starting talking about the hybrid.
出现了一片黑暗
This blackness appeared,
然后越来越大
and it got bigger and bigger
直到把整个西边都挡住了
until it blocked out the west.
"西边"是指什么
What do you mean, "the west"?
不知道  这片黑暗
I don't know. This...black fear.
是从西边来的
It was coming from the west.
而且你每当你说到混血
And whenever you asked about the hybrid,
它就害怕西边
it feared the west.
她就在那
That's where she is.
是的
Yes.
那么我们就要去那儿
Then that's where we're going.
求你了  我不想拥有这些能力
Please, I don't want these powers.
收回去吧  它们越来越强大了
Just take them away. They're getting stronger.
我会伤到别人的
I'm going to hurt someone.
我明白
I understand.
亚蕾克西  不要
Lexi, no.
它们又开始空投食物了
The food drops are back!
-给我  -我拿到了
- Give me that. -I got one.
把你的手拿开
Get your hands off!
慢点  各位
Take it easy, people!
我们要保证每个人都拿到他应得的
Let's make sure everyone gets their fair share!
你们应该知道怎么做
Hey, you boys know better.
老爸
Old man.
那个火焰喷射器做得不错
The flamethrower was a nice touch.
你满意吗  我最后时刻加上的
You liked that? Yeah, I added that last minute.
你去哪儿了
Well, where have you been?
我不是告诉过你别做不理智的事吗
I thought I told you not to do anything crazy.
没有  你说的是别做蠢事
No, you said don't do anything stupid.
你可没说别做不理智的事
You didn't say anything about crazy.
我明白  可我也没有别的办法了
I know. I didn't see another way.
我有
Well, I did.
我找到了一条地下通道  如果我们能
I found an underground tunnel that might come in real handy
想办法破坏电网  就会很方便了
if we can find a way to get that wall down.
我恰好有几个主意能搞定这事
Well, I may have an idea or two on how to do that very thing.
你在飞船上跟它说什么了
So, what did you say to him up there?
它们放了你  还给我们食物
I mean, they let you go, and they gave us food.
我跟它做了笔交易
I made a deal.
-什么  -我跟艾士芬尼做了笔交易
A what? With the Espheni. I made a deal.
我跟它们说我们不会再战斗了
I told them we're not gonna fight anymore
而且也不会再暴动了
and we're not gonna riot.
我没明白你的意思
I don't follow you.
我就是这么做"交易"的
It's my version of "Let's Make a Deal."
你还记不记得你说过所有的答案
You remember when you said all the answers
都在那架飞船上
were on that dirigible?
确实如此
Well, they were.
我们要离开这儿了  畅通无阻
We're getting out of here... all the way out.